## **Rahul Sunil Lokhande**

Github ID = Rahul3012

# **Experience**

December 2019 - June 2020

#### Internship

Completed 6 months of internship in **Emtec Inc**.

June 2020 - September 2020

### **Trainee Software Development Engineer**

Completed 3 months as a trainee in **Emtec Inc.** 

September 2020 - October 2021

### **Associate Software Development Engineer**

Completed as an associate in Emtec Inc.

October 2021

#### **Software Development Engineer**

Working as a Software Development Engineer in Emtec Inc.

# **Experience Summary**

Full stack software developer in Emtec Inc.

2 Years experience in IT industry.

Hands on experience in development in microservices and micro frontend application using .net API, Python, Reactjs, Docker and Kubernetes

Hands on experience in serverless application development with Azure Cloud Services

Have knowledge in Linux kernel development and Linux system programming. (Power Management of USB devices, USB device driver)

### Skills

Programming Languages: Web Programming: Intellectual

C, C++ Javascript Always learn new things

Python React JS Never give up

.Net Angular JS

Java bash

### Course & Certification

**Tools & Technologies** 

Red Hat Certified System Administrator (RHCSA) Red Hat Linux

Red Hat Certified Engineer (RHCE)

Azure

Linux Kernel Development Fundamentals (Linux Foundation) Docker & Kubernetes

DevOps Prerequisites Android Studio

## **Education**

june 2008 - April 2014

City Highschool, Sangli –  $\chi$  grade

Percentage obtained in X grade: 84.80%

August 2014 - May 2017

Government Polytechnic, Miraj - Diploma

Percentage obtained in diploma: 85.37%

August 2017 - May 2020

Rajarambapu Institute of Technology, Islampur - Bachelor of Technology

Pointer obtained in B.Tech: 7.82

# **Sports**

Swimming, Cricket, Badminton, Volleyball, Long Tennis